{
    "subject": "resource/Giovanni_Bondioni",
    "predicate": "ontology/birthDate",
    "object": "1894-09-29",
    "human_readable": "Giovanni Bondioni was born on September 29, 1894.",
    "questions": [
        {
            "score": 0.9134664535522461,
            "question": "When was Giovanni Bondioni born?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.9018820524215698,
            "question": "Who was born on September 29, 1894?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.875663697719574,
            "question": "What is the significance of September 29th for Giovanni Bondioni?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.8135495781898499,
            "question": "What is Giovanni Bondioni's birthdate?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.7624985575675964,
            "question": "On what date did Giovanni Bondioni celebrate his birth?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.7125759124755859,
            "question": "Is Giovanni Bondioni's birth year before or after 1900?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.6855489015579224,
            "question": "September 29th, 1894 is associated with which event?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.5677826404571533,
            "question": "Giovanni Bondioni's birthdate falls in which month?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.5566325783729553,
            "question": "What is Giovanni Bondioni's birth date expressed as month/day/year?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.530331552028656,
            "question": "In what year did Giovanni Bondioni enter the world?"
        }
    ],
    "google_pages": [
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Giovanni Bondioni was born on September 29, 1894.",
            "html": "dbpedia_1801_0.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=What is Giovanni Bondioni's birth date expressed as month/day/year?",
            "html": "dbpedia_1801_1.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Giovanni Bondioni's birthdate falls in which month?",
            "html": "dbpedia_1801_2.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=September 29th, 1894 is associated with which event?",
            "html": "dbpedia_1801_3.html"
        }
    ],
    "selected_docs": [
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_1801_1.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_1801_10.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_1801_20.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_1801_35.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_1801_43.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_1801_55.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_1801_62.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_1801_63.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_1801_67.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_1801_99.txt"
        }
    ],
    "final_question": "Is true?",
    "responses": {
        "gemma2": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{'output': 'yes'}\n``` \n"
        },
        "llama3.1": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "Here is the structured JSON format containing the evaluation of whether the information in the documents supports the triple:\n\n```\n{\n  \"output\": \"yes\"\n}\n```\n\nThis is because the first document contains the following sentence:\n\n\"Giovanni Bondioni marquis of Niardo (September 29, 1894, Niardo \u2013 August 17, 1918, Milovice) was an Italian lieutenant, of the Italian army during the World War I.\"\n\nWhich explicitly states that Giovanni Bondioni was born on September 29, 1894."
        },
        "qwen2.5": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{'output': 'yes'}\n```\n\nThis response is based on the information provided in the documents, which state that \"Giovanni Bondioni marquis of Niardo (September 29, 1894, Niardo \u2013 August 17, 1918, Milovice) was an Italian lieutenant, of the Italian army during the World War I.\" This directly supports the statement that Giovanni Bondioni was born on September 29, 1894."
        },
        "mistral": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": " {\n    \"output\": \"yes\"\n    }"
        }
    },
    "need_tiebreaker": false,
    "tiebreakers_responses": {
        "qwen2.5:14b": {},
        "llama3.1:70b": {}
    },
    "final_decision": 1,
    "actual_decision": 1,
    "analysis": {
        "stratum": "The Least Popular",
        "topic": "-"
    },
    "errors": {}
}